A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Education and Public Policy Division, Office Files of Richard Sharpe FA557
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, International Division, Education and Public Policy Division, Office Files of Richard Sharpe
1960-1981
Rockefeller Archive Center
Sharpe, Richard S.
Ford Foundation
FA557
16.24 Cubic Feet
Arrangement
Arranged in 5 series:
1. Chronological Correspondence.
2. Public Policy and Social Organization Meetings.
3. Future Program Planning Projects.
4. Reports, Conferences, Papers, Reprints.
5. Education, Social Sciences and Public Policy Programming files.
Biographical / Historical
Richard Sharpe worked at the Ford Foundation for over ten years. He worked in the International Division, Latin America and the Caribbean, Brazil program as a Program Advisor before becoming the Foundation's Assistant Representative to Brazil. After that, he moved to the International Division, Office of the Vice President as a Program Officer. He then became a Program Advisor for the Middle East and Africa Program. Later, he served as a Program Officer for the Committee on Public Policy and Social Organization.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Contains a broad spectrum of correspondence, reports, papers, conference and meeting records as well as program planning materials.
- Choronological Correspondence, 1974-1981; I; 2.63 Cubic Feet
  - 1974-1975 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1974 July 1-1975 June 15 (Box 1)
  - 1975 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1975 June 16-December 31 (Box 1)
  - 1976 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1976 January-June (Box 1)
  - 1976 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1976 July-December (Box 1)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1977 January-June (Box 1)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1977 April (Box 1)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1977 May (Box 1)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1977 June (Box 1)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1977 July (Box 1)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1977 August (Box 1)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1977 September (Box 1)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1977 October (Box 1)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1977 November (Box 1)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1977 December (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 January (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 February (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 March (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 April (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 May (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 June (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 July (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 August (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 September (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 October (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 November (Box 1)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1978 December (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 January (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 February (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 March (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 April (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 May (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 June (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 July (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 August (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 September (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 October (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 November (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979 December (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 January (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 February (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 March (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 April (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 May (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 June (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 July (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 August (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 September (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 October (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 November (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1980 December (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1981 January (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1981 February (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1981 March (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1981 April (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1981 May (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1981 June (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1981 July (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1981 August (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1981 September (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1981 October (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, 1981 November (Box 2)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, A-I (Box 2)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, J-P (Box 2)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Q-Z (Box 2)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, A-L (Box 2)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, M-R (Box 2)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, S-Z (Box 2)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, A-G (Box 2)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, H-M (Box 2)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, N-P (Box 2)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Q-Z (Box 2)
- Public Policy and Social Organization Meetings, 1969-1981; II; 6.57 Cubic Feet
  - Public Policy and Social Organization Meeting Minutes, Agendas and Materials, 1973-1981; II.1
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 4, 1973 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), 1973 October 4 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 20, 1973 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), 1973 December 20 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 10, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), 1974 January 10 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 31, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), 1974 January 31 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 21, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), 1974 February 21 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 21, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), 1974 March 21 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 18, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), 1974 April 18 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 15, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), 1974 May 15 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 14, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), 1974 June 14 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 19, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1974 July 19 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of August 22, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1974 August 22 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 20, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1974 September 20 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 17, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1974 October 17 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 14, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1974 November 14 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 11, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1974 December 11 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 9, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1975 January 9 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 6, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1975 February 6 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 20, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1975 February 20 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 28, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1975 March 28 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 1, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1975 May 1 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 15, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1975 March 15 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 13, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1975 June 13 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 23, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1975 July 23 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 25, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1975 September 25 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 30, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1975 October 30 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 25, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1975 November 25 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 8, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 January 8 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 2, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 February 2 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 4, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 March 4 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 1, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 April 1 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 14, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 April 14 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 18, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 May 18 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 16, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 June 16 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 29, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 July 29 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 9, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 September 9 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 12, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 October 12 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 10, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 November 10 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 15, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1976 December 15 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 11, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1977 January 11 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 17, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1977 February 17 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 31, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1977 March 31 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 28, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1977 April 28 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 21, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1977 June 21 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 28, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1977 July 28 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 19, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1977 September 19 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 18, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1977 October 18 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 17, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1977 November 17 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 15, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials, incl. David Heaps' report "An Inquiry on the "Values" Project"), 1977 December 15 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 19, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1978 January 19 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 16, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1978 February 16 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 16, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1978 March 16 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 20, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1978 April 20 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 18, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1978 May 18 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 15, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1978 June 15 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 27, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1978 July 27 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 14, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1978 September 14 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 12, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1978 October 12 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 16, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1978 November 16 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 13, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1978 December 13 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 24, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1979 January 24 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 21, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1979 February 21 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 27, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1979 March 27 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 18, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1979 April 18 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 15, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1979 May 15 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 19, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1979 June 19 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 24, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1979 July 24 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 18, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1979 September 18 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 16, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1979 October 16 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 20, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1979 November 20 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 18, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1979 December 18 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 15, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1980 January 15 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 19, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1980 February 19 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 18, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1980 March 18 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 15, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1980 April 15 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 20, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1980 May 20 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 17, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1980 June 17 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of August 19, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1980 August 19 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 17, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1980 September 17 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 21, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials) (1 of 2), 1980 October 21 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 21, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials) (2 of 2), 1980 October 21 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 19, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1980 November 19 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 16, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1980 December 16 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 20, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1981 January 20 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 17, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1981 February 17 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 17, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1981 March 17 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 22, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1981 April 22 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 19, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1981 May 19 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 16, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1981 June 16 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 21, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1981 July 21 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 15, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), 1981 September 15 (Box 6)
    - PPSO -- Annual Report Notes/Memoranda and Budget Paper for March Board of Trustees Meeting (incl. Henry Ford II resignation letter), 1977 (Box 6)
    - "Report of PPSO Task Force on the Military and Society" by Enid C.B. Schoettle, 1980 May 23 (Box 6)
    - Women's Program Group -- Summary of Meeting (May 30, 1980) with Section on Education and Public Policy, 1980 June (Box 6)
  - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Proposals and Recommendations, 1969-1981; II.2
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations, 1969-1973 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations, 1974-1976 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 7)
    - Grants Re: Public Policy Programs at American Universities (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 7)
    - Grants Re: Public Policy Programs at American Universities (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 7)
- Future Program Planning Project, 1975-1976; III; 3.94 Cubic Feet
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File I (Pre-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (1 of 5), 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File I (Pre-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (2 of 5), 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File I (Pre-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (3 of 5), 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File I (Pre-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (4 of 5), 1975 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File I (Pre-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (5 of 5), 1975 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File II (Post-Mt. Kisco Meeting), 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File II (Post-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (2 of 4), 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File II (Post-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File II (Post-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- June-July Meetings (Mt. Kisco) -- Summaries, Speeches, etc. (1 of 2), 1976 June-July (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- June-July Meetings (Mt. Kisco) -- Summaries, Speeches, etc. (2 of 2), 1976 June-July (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- Key Documents (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- Key Documents (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- Documents Given to Trustees at June/July Meetings, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- Memoranda Re: Foundation Priority Areas, Preparation of FPPP Discussion Papers, etc., 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- Outsiders Names Re: Paper Writing, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- Master List, circa 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Schultz, Theodore -- "The Hungry, Crowded, Competitive World", 1976 February 26 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Islam, Nurul - "Hungry, Crowded and Competitive World", circa 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Legesse, Asmarom -- "Hunger and Population", circa 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Geertz, Clifford and Albert Hirschman -- Conversation Transcript, 1976 January 27 (Box 8)